

Yann PIVEL

26 years old



+33 6 37 21 46 33



Metz, France



yann.pivel@hotmail.fr

EDUCATION

Web and mobile web developer training AFPA – Distance learning **2021- In progress**

BTS BANQUE Retail Market GRETA - Reims 2014

BAC STG Marketing option Lycée Jean Talon 2012

— LANGUAGES —

French: Native
English: Fluent
German: Notions

INTÉRÊTS

Football

Music

Cooking





PROFILE

After more than 8 years of experience in the Customer Service sector, I have taken the opportunity to retrain as a Web Developer. As part of my current training, I am looking for an internship in a company from 02 November 2021 to 14 January 2022.

SKILLS

- Consulting, negotiation and commercial management (B to B and B to C)
- Tutoring, recruitment, team and site management
- Development of supplier and partner relationships
- Management of a portfolio in an unpaid situation, analysis of the causes and search for amicable solutions
- Ability to make decisions and proposals
- Handling of telephone and email disputes (FR/ENG)
- Creation of a Wordpress website (<u>www.les-bulles-de-julie.fr</u>)



















WORK EXPERIENCE

From 02/09/2012 to 14/09/2015 (Reims, France)

NATIXIS FINANCEMENT

Collection Agent

After two years of work experience (BTS Bank) as a sales agent in the collections department, I moved on to the position of Collections Manager, where my tasks were to search for unreachable customers, enter into contact with them and, above all, negotiate the terms of repayment of unpaid debts and set up an amicable and lasting solution.

From 10/11/2015 to 06/06/2016 (Epernay, France)

CREDIT AGRICOLE

Commercial Advisor

As a receptionist and then tutor for new recruits, I moved on to a position as a sales advisor in charge of developing my portfolio and my sales actions by optimising customer satisfaction.

From 27/10/2016 to 15/03/2018 (Orléans, France)

ENTERPRISE RENT-A-CAR

Agency Manager

As an efficient and committed advisor, I progressed early on to the position of site manager. With a team of 7 people, we managed to triple the size of the fleet and double the agency's profits while developing relationships with partners and suppliers and managing the fleet.

From 28/05/2018 to 27/09/2019 (Swords, Irlande)

HERTZ – EUROPEAN HEADQUARTERS

Customer Service Representative

After 10 months in the internet and telephone reservation customer service (English and French speaking), thanks to my knowledge of procedures, I moved to the customer service department, then my good results led me to the management and resolution of complex and delicate cases in close collaboration with the legal department.

From 31/10/2019 to 30/09/2020 (Luxembourg, Luxembourg)

AVIS/BUDGET GROUP

Rental Sales Agent

Assigned to the Gare du Luxembourg branch, my role was to relaunch the business as well as to manage the vehicle fleet, customer reception and delivery as well as the dispatch of the various vehicle preparers.